Chapter 1300: Soft Gold Mine

Zhao Hai’s body appeared inside a tunnel. This was a tunnel inside the soft gold mine. Zhao Hai handed over the weapon refining task over to Cai’er while he returned to the mine. His purpose this time was to get more Demons for the Space so that he could increase the Space’s beasts’ fighting strength as soon as possible.

The weapons used by Yuan and the others had a lot of requirements. Moreover, plenty of these weapons were nonmetal. Instead, they used some special wood or bones from Demons.

These kinds of things were no longer useful for the Space, but they were good for refining weapons. Although there wasn’t any shortage of these things in the Space, Zhao Hai wouldn’t deny having more. And since Yuan and the others wished for him to make them good weapons, then he would naturally comply.

The Universal Processing Machine was formidable because of its two functions: to make any material into weapons and also fusing two materials together which was almost impossible to fuse in any other way.

The weapons that Yuan and the others use were simple weapons made by the Machine Field. The reason why they have high requirements for their weapons was because of their experience in fighting in the Six Realms Battlefield. At the same time, they also had deep understanding regarding the weapons used by the other realms. Even Sprites, who fought mainly with their summons, use artifacts. If someone from the Machine Field wanted to contend against people from the other realms, then they would need a weapon specially made for them. Naturally, it would be better if the weapon had weapon shattering.

However, weapon shattering had a high requirement when it came to weapons. The more weapon shattering weapons a weapon has, the more high-quality materials it would need. This was because ordinary materials don’t have the means to withstand the pressure of weapon shattering.

Most metals couldn’t handle this intense shaking. Therefore, these metals needed to be fused with other materials such as special wood or bones.

These special wood and Demon bones couldn’t just be simply classified as wood or bones. One should know that these things were mostly from weapons from all kinds of environments and were excellent materials. Whether they were wood or bones, they could be considered as treasures of the heavens and earth. Their properties could be used in all kinds of manners.

And before using these materials, Zhao Hai also ran them under the Universal Scanner in order to analyze their properties. Fusing them into artifacts wouldn’t reduce the artifact’s strength. Instead, this fusion would instead cause the artifact to be more powerful.

Zhao Hai had a lot of ores inside the Space. However, he doesn’t intend to abuse these ores. Take soft gold, for example, if he used it in everyone’s weapon, then how could he explain where he got them? One shouldn’t think that Yuan and the others don’t know anything about refining. A weapon was a Warrior’s second life, so how could Yuan and the others not know about them? If they discover anything suspicious, then Zhao Hai would find it hard to explain.

After seeing that the weapon refining was going well, Zhao Hai shifted his attention to Jia Ding Shan. Jia Ding Shan was currently busy teaching the pangolins in the Space. These iron armor beasts have become very smart. Jia Ding Shan also discovered that they were very suitable for Cultivation. Zhao Hai arranged 1000 iron armor beasts to be taught to cultivate. At this point, these pangolins were almost equivalent to Qi Condensation-stage Cultivators.

Jia Ding Shan was very satisfied with this result. One must know that it wasn’t easy for a Demon to reach Qi Condensation. As long as a Demon reached this stage, however, their Cultivation would become smoother.

Actually, for Demons, Qi Condensation was akin to building their foundation for practice. Once this foundation was established, then their later stages would become easier. But if this foundation wasn’t properly set up, then they would face disadvantages in their further practice.

The Pangolin Family wasn’t a huge clan in the Demon Realm. They also weren’t as powerful as the Mouse Race. The Mouse Race can be considered to be a medium-sized power in the Demon Realm. This was because they had a large population, allowing them more disciples to train. And the more Mouse they could train, the more powerful they would become, and in turn they would get more resources. And the more resources they get, the more Mice they can train. It was an upward cycle.

This was also the development cycle for other influences in the World of Cultivation. This explained why, despite being in a rich environment, small sects were still having difficulties expanding.

Jia Ding Shan was now Zhao Hai’s servant. He taught these pangolins not only to make them stronger, but to also train a group of soldiers for Zhao Hai.

Hao Sha was also the same. Zhao Hai arranged some mice for him to train. His results were also doing great. Although Hao Sha was now an Undead, he could still pass on his cultivation method to the other mice. After seeing that this project was doing great, he prepared to leave for the soft gold mine.

The soft gold mine was too chaotic. Every day, groups of differing numbers arrive in order to hunt other people. This made this place the best place to kill people.

Zhao Hai stood in the tunnel of the soft gold mine and looked around. There was nobody present – as he had seen in the Space. This time, Zhao Hai changed his appearance and wore cultivator robes. He also didn’t hold his staff and instead stepped on a silver sword as he flew.

No matter who sees him, they would regard Zhao Hai as a Cultivator. Nobody would think that he was a Mage from the Machine Field. Zhao Hai also didn’t inform Yuan and the others that he would be hunting people in the soft gold mine. One must know that everyone was currently thinking that he was refining weapons.

Zhao Hai doesn’t think that news in the soft gold mine wouldn’t reach Yuan and the others. One shouldn’t underestimate the means of communication of people in the Six Realms Battlefield. In this place where computers were popular, all kinds of communication methods emerged endlessly. Zhao Hai had no confidence that his presence here would remain unknown. Therefore, he can only change his appearance.

After looking around him, Zhao Hai chose a direction and flew along it. Zhao Hai was here to kill people, so he doesn’t care about who he came across.

Not long after Zhao Hai began flying, he met a team of ten people. Unexpectedly they were Spirits. Although Zhao Hai hadn’t fought with them before ,he didn’t avoid them and directly flew in their direction.

These Spirit Cultivators were also quick to discover Zhao Hai. They also didn’t avoid him and instead waited for him to arrive. Although these Spirit Cultivators were only at Core Formation, in their minds, ten people besieging Zhao Hai should be enough to deal with him.

It was very rare for two groups to speak when they met each other in the soft gold mine. If their strength was the same, then maybe they can negotiate to leave. But if one side was strong while the other was weak, then the stronger party wouldn’t hesitate to make a move. At this point, communication was unnecessary.

This was also the reason why Zhao Hai didn’t talk and just immediately engaged the group of Spirit Cultivators. The Spirit Cultivators rely on their spirits to attack. And Core Formation Spirit Cultivators couldn’t be underestimated. Once Zhao Hai approached, they immediately unleashed a large amount of spirits to attack.

Some of these combat spirits were spirits captured by the Spirit Cultivators and made into their own summons. The strength of a spirit was generally related to their master. Spirits also have some intelligence of their own. If a spirit was too strong for their master, then the spirit might devour their master. Therefore, spirits used by the Spirit Cultivators were those on the same level as them or a level lower. In this case, they relied on numbers to win.

Besides combat spirits, the Sprites also have their life source spirits. Their life source spirits were different compared to the Sprite Race’s life source spirits. A Sprite’s life source spirit was a spirit that was generated by splitting their own soul. They could command them freely and make them attack their enemies. This made them terrifying on the battlefield.

On the other hand, a Spirit Cultivator generally won’t let their own life source spirit participate in the battle. The connection between a Spirit Cultivator and their life source spirit was too intimate. Any damage done to the life source spirit would heavily impact the Spirit Cultivator.

When Zhao Hai saw these combat spirits, he smiled faintly before releasing large quantities of Undead as well as Hao Sha.

Seeing the Undead, the Spirit Cultivators immediately knew that they were in trouble. However, it was already too late for them to run away since the Undead had surrounded them. Zhao Hai didn’t give the Spirit Cultivators and opportunity to attack as he immediately ordered the Undead to attack.

Due to Zhao Hai’s presence as well as Hao Sha and the other Undead, the battle was finished quickly. Zhao Hai also made the Spirit Cultivators into his Undead.

After obtaining the Spirit Cultivators, Zhao Hai immediately cleaned the battlefield. He doesn’t want to leave any traces otherwise people might find him for trouble.

It must be said that there were a lot of people in the soft gold mine. Zhao Hai didn’t need to fly far before he met another group. This time, he met a group of 15 Demons. This was a group of Core Formation Demons led by a Nascent Soul Demon. Zhao Hai wasn’t polite and released large quantities of Undead as well as Hao Sha. The other party was destroyed completely in a blink of an eye. This team of Demons comprised various races. There were Snakes, Toads, Ox, Bears, and the Nascent Soul Demon which was a Hawk.

These races were enemies before they achieved their spiritual wisdom. But after they developed intelligence, they belonged to one race, the Demon Race. Now that he gained a lot of Demons, Zhao Hai didn’t stay in the soft gold mine. He returned to the Space and arranged for more beasts to be taught cultivation.

Chapter 1301: Zheng Li’s Difficulty

Zhao Hai returned to the Space right after because he didn’t want to attract too much attention. Although murder was very common in the soft gold mine, if he killed too many people in a short time, then people with power will take note of his presence. When that time comes, hunting peacefully would be impossible.

Getting attention was great, but too much wasn’t good. If Zhao Hai excessively slaughters people in the soft gold mine, then all races there will be alerted. When the time comes, it wouldn’t just become Zhao Hai’s matter, but also the entire Machine Field.

One must know that the other realms had been drooling for a long time for the Machine Field’s territory. But since they had problems with each other, they couldn’t form an alliance. Additionally, the people of the Machine Field in the Six Realms Battlefield weren’t easy to deal with. This allowed the Machine Field to defend their own territory in the battlefield. But even with this, their partially controlled territory was still smaller compared to the other realms.

Zhao Hai wanted to kill people in order to strengthen the Space. However, he didn’t want to cause trouble for the Machine Field. If he implicated the Machine Field, then he would not only suffer but the civilians in the realm as well.

Upon returning to the Space, Zhao Hai looked at what Yuan and the others were doing. Yuan and the others were biding their time. The Sprites also knew that they would retaliate since it was Yuan’s style. Yuan was waiting for the weapons refined by Zhao Hai. As long as Zhao Hai finished refining the weapons, then their combat strength would be increased. Most importantly, with Zhao Hai being a powerful expert, they were confident in causing trouble with the Sprites.

Seeing that Yuan and the others didn’t make a move, Zhao Hai relaxed. Then he looked at Laura and said, “How is it? Did you manage to map the soft gold mine?”

Laura nodded and said, “The entire soft gold mine has been mapped. The place is really chaotic. There are people fighting at any time.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but chuckle at the chaos in the soft gold mine. He already experienced it for himself. And now that the entire mine has been mapped, he can appear anywhere inside it.

The soft gold ore in the mine was close to being depleted. If this decreases even more, then the other realms might restrain their people from going to the mine. This was because they might not be able to withstand the casualties.

However, Zhao Hai wanted to use this opportunity to plant soft gold ores from the Space into the mine. This way, people would maintain hope that the mine still has more supply.

Speaking of which, only people from the Machine Field rarely went to the soft gold mine. This was mainly because their strength wasn’t good – only a few could manage to survive. Therefore, although the other realms were killing each other in the mines, people from the Machine Field rarely joined.

And as long as there was chaos in the soft gold mine, the Machine Field would be able to go to other parts of the battlefield to harvest resources. This chaos also reduced the pressure on Lock Mountain Range.

Before Yuan entered the Six Realms Battlefield, the Lock Mountain range was close to being turned into another soft gold mine. The other realms would go there to hunt people, dig ores, or harvest herbs. There were endless attacks conducted on the Machine Field. In their minds, as long as these attacks continue, people of the Machine Field might get tired of fighting and abandon the mountain range. This would give the other realms a larger area of activities, and in turn more resources.

From the past several days, Zhao Hai understood that the Lock Mountain Range also had patches of mineable areas. These were minerals unique only to the Machine Field. Some of these minerals would be used by the realm and the rest would be used to trade with the other realms. It can be said that the Six Realms Battlefield was the main source of foreign exchange resources of the Machine Field. If they lost Lock Mountain Range, then it would be a huge blow to the Machine Field.

After Yuan and the others went all out to fight the other realms, the other realms began to feel the pain of their losses and lessen their pressure on the Machine Field. At the same time, the soft gold mine became more chaotic, attracting more people from the other realms which in turn lessened the pressure on Lock Mountain Range much more. This was the reason why the mountain range was peaceful when Zhao Hai and the others arrived. In the past, it was common for experts like Hao Sha to attack the forts.

Zhao Hai doesn’t want the chaos in the soft gold mine to stop. The more chaotic it was, the calmer the Lock Mountain Range would be. In any case, the Space was producing soft gold ore now. Injecting some soft gold ore into the soft gold mine would certainly cause people to turn frantic.

Seeing Zhao Hai smiling, Lizzy smiled as well. Then she said, “Big Brother Hai, while we were receiving information about the soft gold mine, we also saw an acquaintance there.”

Zhao Hai immediately asked, “Acquaintance? Who?”

Lizzy waved towards the screen, then it showed a scene with a group of Cultivators. The strength of this group wasn’t that great. Most of these Cultivators looked like beginners. But their leader was a Nascent Soul Expert. And in this group was indeed an acquaintance of Zhao Hai, it was Suo Liancheng.

Upon seeing Suo Liancheng, Zhao Hai gawked. He didn’t expect to see Suo Liancheng here. To be honest, Zhao Hai had a good impression towards Suo Liancheng. He knew when to retreat and when to attack. He also had a straightforward personality. It’s just a pity that they belong to competing realms.

Zhao Hai said, “I didn’t expect him to also be in the Six Realms Battlefield. I’ll meet him when I have the time.”

Lizzy and the others smiled. They knew that Zhao Hai quite liked Suo Liancheng. This was why Lizzy told Zhao Hai this news.

After looking through the soft gold mine, Zhao Hai moved to take care of his newly procured Demon Undead. They were allocated planets as well as students to teach. And just like Hao Shai and Jia Ding Shan, each Demon Undead were given 1000 students.

Jia Ding Shan was very relaxed recently. After all, the iron armor beasts were very obedient. This made teaching them very easy.

Once he was done with these things, Zhao Hai decided to take a rest. But then, Cai’er’s expression suddenly changed. Then she turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, a bug tide just occured in Fabio Planet. Mister Zheng Li is in danger.”

Upon hearing Cai’er, Zhao Hai stared. Then he immediately commanded Cai’er to show the situation on Fabio Planet. Shown on the screen was the situation of Base Number 5. At this moment, the base was besieged by large quantities of Bugs. There weren’t only eight-legged bugs present, there were also praying mantis as well as bugs that Zhao Hai had not seen before. These bugs were surrounding the entire base. But what made it worse was that the walls of Base Number 5 had been broken through, causing the bugs to stream into the Base.

Zheng Li was Base Number 5’s commander. At this time, he was commanding Cultivators to drive off the bugs. However, they were being slowly grinded down. If this continues, then they would reach a very critical situation.

Zhao Hai was dumbfounded when he saw this. He also experienced a bug tide. In the last bug tide, there were a lot of reinforcements to support the base. The transmission formation lit up continuously as experts streamed in. But why wasn’t this the case this time?

Before long, Zhao Hai noticed that the transmission formations weren’t flashing. This meant that the base wasn’t being reinforced. This caused Zhao Hai to be puzzled. He immediately shifted the display to the transmission formation. But upon looking at the formation, Zhao Hai was shocked. Base Number 5’s transmission formation was actually seized by the Bugs.

There was no mistaking it, the transmission formation has been seized. Zhao Hai also saw that there was a large hole just outside the formation. This hole was quite enormous with a diameter exceeding 20 meters. Moreover, it was very deep. It was clear that it was being dug by the bugs. At the same time, there were two Silverback Gold-winged bugs above the formations, fighting off two Nascent Soul Experts. In addition to the two, there were also a large number of bugs standing on the transmission formations.

Zhao Hai hadn’t seen these bugs before. These bugs weren’t big. They had black-brown color and had eight feet. The six hindlegs were used for mobility while the two forelegs were able to be freely moved.

It was clear that the fighting strength of these bugs wasn’t strong. However, their speed of excavation was very quick. These insects were currently destroying the transmission formations.

Upon seeing these bugs, Zhao Hai began to understand where the large hole came from. It was also because of these bugs that Base Number 5 wasn’t getting any reinforcements.

Zhao Hai was shocked by the implications of this scene. This meant that the bugs had discovered the weakness of the transmission formations. As long as a living creature stood on top of the transmission formation, then it couldn’t be used. However, this weakness had never been discovered by the bugs before. This allowed multiple bug tides to be repelled.

But this time, not only was this attack deliberate, it was also well-organized. First, they had bugs that could dig very deep underneath the base, bypassing the alarms of the base. And then the bugs used this tunnel to perform an attack on the base while also blocking the transmission formations. This isolated Base Number 5 from the rest of the bases.

In order to complete this plan, the Bugs sent two Silverback Gold-winged bugs. The role of these Silverback Gold-winged bugs was to defend the insects on the transmission formations. As long as they held on, the Cultivators wouldn’t be able to get reinforcements.

One has to recognize that the move of the bugs this time was very extraordinary. They hit the weakness of Base Number 5. With no reinforcements, Base Number 5 would be courting death if they kept fighting the bugs.

Chapter 1302: Two Choices

Intelligent….too intelligent!

When Zhao Hai saw the actions made by the bugs, he couldn’t help but sigh. The bugs were indeed smart. Although he had already confirmed the intelligence of the bugs back when he was in Base Number 5, it seems like the bugs were becoming smarter and smarter. This wasn’t good.

Zhao Hai didn’t immediately move to save Zheng Li. Base Number 5 wouldn’t be falling that soon. Even if the base has been broken through, there were still a lot of Cultivators that could defend it. At this moment, Zheng Li was still organizing people to fight bugs on the street.

Zhao Hai frowned as he considered what to do. Should he just save Zheng Li or the entire Base Number 5?

Zhao Hai wasn’t overestimating himself. This was because he was truly strong enough. He has more than enough Undead to kill the bugs, saving the base from being surrounded on all sides.

However, if he did use such an above board method, then it would surely bring him trouble. Therefore, Zhao Hai couldn’t make up his mind at this time.

Laura and the others were also waiting for Zhao Hai to make a decision. They were looking at the monitor. The bugs and Cultivators were fighting each other. The Cultivators were in a battle formation as they defended against the bug assault. However, the bugs were endless. There were also flying bugs that managed to pick off a Cultivator once in a while.

Seeing Zhao Hai knitting his brows, Laura couldn’t help but ask, “Brother Hai? What are you thinking about?”

Zhao Hai looked at the screen and said, “Do you think I should solve Base Number 5’s problem or just rescue Brother Zheng Li?”

When she heard this, Laura paused for a moment. Then she answered, “Brother Hai, I think it’s best for us if you just save Brother Zheng Li. We cannot do anything about Base Number 5. Even if it’s a good thing, you should know about the trouble that it would bring us. So why are you still hesitating?”

Zhao Hai gave a nod. Then he said, “I’m hesitating because of the Bug Race. Their ability to evolve is too formidable. And they seem to be getting smarter now. The Cultivators have been keeping them back all this time. But once the bugs evict the Cultivators from the planet, then I’m afraid they would start conquering other planets. If this happens, then the entire World of Cultivation would face a crisis.”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “Brother Hai, it wouldn’t be that serious. You’re underestimating the strength of the Cultivation Realm. If you count the entire realm, they have a large number of Nascent Soul Experts. We already knew about how strong they are. And what of those stronger than them? Moreover, the Great Sects had existed for many years, their foundation is very solid. The Bugs can reproduce quickly and their ability to evolve was indeed powerful. However, the Cultivation Realm isn’t that weak. I believe that you shouldn’t care about the Bugs for now. Rescue Brother Zheng Li first. He’s a Rogue Cultivator yet he was able to reach his current position. This meant that he has good talent. And as long as you can find a way to receive his family, then Brother Zheng Li might become your subordinate. As for Fabio Planet, you shouldn’t be worried. If the Bugs act, then the Cultivation Realm’s attention would be pointed towards them. This would make us breathe easier. We can seize this opportunity to grow our power.”

Zhao Hai listened to Laura’s words and thought that what she said was reasonable. The bugs could pull attention away from him. Not only could his development become smoother, this event would also impact the equilibrium of the Six Realms Battlefield. No matter what, this was a good thing.

Upon thinking up to this point, Zhao Hai gave a slight nod. Seeing Zhao Hai’s appearance, Laura smiled and said, “Also, if the Bugs truly becomes a problem, then we could use it as an opportunity to enter Fabio Planet. From what we saw, bug nests are beneficial to the Space. As long as we get more, then the Space’s strength would increase.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, then let’s rescue Brother Zheng Li first. However, we cannot reveal the Space to him. Let’s take him to the Six Realms Battlefield.” Laura nodded and said, “But we can’t do it right now. There are still a lot of people left in Base Number 5. If we rescue Brother Zheng Li right now, then people from Base Number 5 will notice us. We should wait first. I believe that the Cultivators wouldn’t get annihilated in the base. Even if the transmission formations couldn’t be used, they can still fly away. Once they escape from Base Number 5, they would certainly be chased down by the bugs. When the time comes, we can rescue Brother Zheng Li.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Alright, then let’s do that.”

The situation in Base Number 5 was still shown on the screen. The Silverback Gold-winged Bugs were still defending the transmission formation while the other bugs were destroying the transmission formations. Although the two Nascent Soul Experts of Base Number 5 were doing all they could, they were unable to move the Silverback Gold-winged bugs.

The Silverback Gold-winged bugs were already stronger than them. If the two bugs weren’t defending the transmission formation and fought seriously, then the two Nascent Soul Cultivators would be destroyed.

The two Nascent Soul Cultivators were also aware of this. However, they need to clear the transmission formation. If they cannot solve this problem, then Base Number 5 will be conquered.

One should know that building a base in Fabio Planet wasn’t an easy task. Each base cost a lot of resources as well as lives in order to be built. Losing a base meant losing one foothold on the planet. Then sooner or later, the Cultivation Realm would be expelled from the planet.

Therefore, people from the Cultivation Realm wouldn’t just let a base be destroyed. As long as they have hope, then they will defend the base at all costs.

The entire Base Number 5 has devolved into a hopeless mess. Zheng Li already knew that Base Number 5 was finished. There were already a lot of bugs inside the base, and now, their transmission formations weren’t working, starving them of reinforcements. In this case, wanting to hold on to Base Number 5 was simply wishful thinking.

But the present issue was that even if they don’t defend Base Number 5, wanting to escape from the bugs would still be very difficult. The Cultivation Realm’s bases in Fabio Planet which were linked by transmission formations were very far from each other. It was also very dangerous to go from base to base without going through a transmission formation. This was because there were a lot of bugs present between two bases.

When he thought of this, Zheng Li couldn’t help but bitterly smile. The Cultivation Realm had been relying on transmission formations. Now that the base had lost its transmission formations, they can’t retreat.

Although this was the case, Zheng Li didn’t give up in resisting. This was because he knew that their opponents weren’t like the other realms in the World of Cultivation. If it was the other races, then once they surrender, then they would stop attacking. However, what they were facing were the bug races. If they surrendered, then they can only be regarded as food.

What Zheng Li was worried about wasn’t his life, but instead his family. His family members were just commoners. Because of his cultivation, Zheng Li’s family was able to enjoy a higher quality of life. If he died here, then his family would return to their original status. This wasn’t something that he wanted to see.

Most Rogue Cultivators in the Cultivation Realm practice for their family. They want their families to stop being farm animals and slaves. And in order for their family to not return to this state, they had to practice hard.

Including him, Zheng Li’s family consists of six people. His grandfather had passed away but his grandmother was still alive. Then there’s his parents, and then his younger brother and younger sister.

Zheng Li’s father was also practicing. However, since his talent was less than Zheng Li, he was stuck in Qi Refining, not even Foundation Establishment. His father did tasks every day in order to support Zheng Li’s brother and sister’s training and also to feed the family.

Zheng Li’s Mother and Grandmother was even worse, only at Body Tempering. So they could only farm. As for Zheng Li’s younger brother, his talent was good. At 20 years old, he was able to reach Qi Refining. As for his sister, it was even better. She managed to reach Qi Refining at 15 years old. Naturally, reaching this state before 20 years old had a lot to do with Zheng Li. Now that he was a Core Formation Cultivator, he was able to give his brother and sister some pills once in a while. Therefore, they were able to quickly progress. With his brother’s speed, it wouldn’t be long before he would be admitted to the Outer Sect.

However, if Zheng Li died here, then all of these plans would vanish. There was an age limit for Sects to recruit disciples. Even if you reach the required level, if your age passed the limit then you wouldn’t be able to enter. Without the pills that Zheng Li provides, his brother and sister wouldn’t be able to enter a sect in their entire lives.

This doesn’t mean that Zheng Li was looking down on his brother and sister. To be honest, although the talent of his brother and sister was good, it wasn’t that much. Without the support of pills, it would be very difficult for them to enter a sect. One must know that the Cultivation Realm wasn’t short of manpower. Great Sects were very meticulous in the selection of their disciples. Therefore, if one wants to be selected, then they need to show talent. This would guarantee the sect’s strength.

But even if Zheng Li wanted to live, he still needed the permission of the bugs. When he thought of this, Zheng Li couldn’t help but feel a bitter taste in his mouth. He was a Core Formation Expert. He only needed to wait for two years before he could get out of the Planet and become an Elder of a Sect. Although he might not have any influence, at the very least he would get the treatment of an Elder. This will make his brother and sister cultivate better. However, he didn’t expect the bugs to become more and more powerful. And this time, he couldn’t even choose to escape.

Although he was feeling despair, Zheng Li didn’t give up in resisting. This was because he knew that as long as he held on, then a chance to survive might appear. If he gave up, then this chance would disappear.

The fight went on as more and more bugs arrived. Moreover, the strength of the bugs was increasing. A mosquito-type bug had entered the fray. This was a bug that Zhao Hai hadn’t seen before. This bug was quite strong with strength equivalent to a Core Formation Expert.

Once these bugs joined in, the situation in Base Number 5 got out of control. Cultivators were beginning to desert. If not for the two Nascent Soul Cultivators, then the entire battle formation would have collapsed.

One shouldn’t overestimate an average Cultivator’s willpower. Since Cultivators value their lives even more than an average person, their willpower easily crumbles when they face an unwinnable situation. When that situation comes, deserting was quite common.

The two Nascent Soul Experts were also having a very bad time. Although they were Nascent Soul Experts, there were a lot of people like them in the Cultivation Realm. Even if they flee, they would still be punished. The Sects had their own rules, and the loss of Base Number 5 was a very huge sin.

However, as more and more bugs stream into the base, the Nascent Soul Experts began to consider their own safety. Between the choice of death or punishment, naturally they would rather be punished than die here. Death was the end, and this was something that Cultivators would never accept.

When the two Nascent Soul Experts looked like they were going to retreat, two Goldspine Bugs suddenly appeared.

Goldspine Bugs and Silverback Gold-winged Bugs looked similar. The only difference between the two of them was that the Goldspine Bug had a sharp horn on its head. This horn could move and when it does it would be like a spear. This bug had the same reputation as the Silverback Gold-winged bugs.

Not only do the Goldspine Bugs have the same reputation as the Silverback Gold-winged Bugs, they were also as strong. They were bugs with Nascent Soul-level strength. When these two bugs appeared, the two Nascent Soul Cultivators immediately ran away. This was because they knew that they had no capability to block four Nascent Soul-level enemies.

And as soon as the two experts ran away, the chaos in Base Number 5 entered its climax. Other Cultivators in the base decided to run as well. Before long, all resistance that Base Number 5 had, vanished. Seeing this situation, Zheng Li couldn’t help but sigh. Although Base Number 5 was his responsibility, he also wanted to save his life.

Chapter 1303: Riverpond City

But how could the bugs just let the people from Base Number 5 withdraw safely? To the bugs, land wasn’t the most important thing. After all, the entire underground of the planet was their domain. To them, the area where Base Number 5 was built on wasn’t attractive. What they were attracted to were the people in Base Number 5.

The Bugs wanted to eat people in order to ingest their genes and evolve. Therefore, the main target of the bugs this time was the inhabitants of Base Number 5.

Now that the Cultivators in Base Number 5 have been routed, and their spirits totally crushed, the bugs began to chase them down with ease.

Several mosquito bugs were chasing behind Zheng Li. Although Zheng Li wanted to get free from them, he could not. This was because the strength of these mosquito bugs was similar to him.

Zheng Li was now despairing. He was alone, only the bugs were chasing behind him. And he was still very far away from another base. If this continued, then he would surely be overtaken by the bugs. He had just experienced a battle, so his energy was very low. He cannot support flying for a long time.

However, Zheng Li struggled for survival since childhood, so he didn’t know how to give up. He knew that opportunities were always at any corner. However, this opportunity might not come in a long time. If you give up, then this opportunity would disappear. As long as there was a chance for survival, Zheng Li wouldn’t give up.

When Zheng Li left Base Number 5, he headed directly towards Base Number 3, the nearest Base. A swarm of mosquito bugs were chasing him relentlessly, leaving him with no opportunity for rest.

At this time, Zheng Li discovered that large quantities of praying mantis bugs appeared in front of him. Although the strength of these praying mantises was inferior to the mosquitos, they were much more numerous. They were enough to tie down Zheng Li.

Zheng Li was also aware that if he was tied down by these mantises, then he would die. However, his current problem was that he didn’t have anywhere to hide. And flying straight upwards was impossible. Zheng Li was currently stuck.

At this time, a spatial rift appeared close to where Zheng Li was. Then Zhao Hai walked out of the rift. While Zheng Li was stunned, Zhao Hai quickly said, “Walk in, quick.” Then he pulled Zheng Li into the spatial rift. As Zheng Li vanished, the bugs were confused. They quickly buzzed around the general area where Zheng Li disappeared.

To the bugs, Zheng Li was their prey. Now that their prey had disappeared, they need to look for him.

While Zheng Li was confused about Zhao Hai’s presence, they appeared inside a cave. Inside the cave was a residence, it seems to have been built for some time.

Zheng Li sobered up. Then he looked at Zhao Hai in surprise and said, “Little Hai, how did you show up here? Where is this?”

Zhao Hai looked at Zheng Li and then smiled faintly, “I don’t know if Brother Zheng Li has heard of this place. But this is the Six Realms Battlefield!”

“The Six Realms Battlefield? This is the Six Realms Battlefield?” Zheng Li also heard about this place from a friend in Base Number 5. Although the man didn’t go to the Six Realms Battlefield, he told Zheng Li about it to show off. He said that being able to go to the Six Realms Battlefield was an affirmation of one’s strength.

Zhao Hai looked at Zheng Li’s reaction and smiled, “Right, this is the Six Realms Battlefield. I came here after the competition. I’m resting and had the urge to contact Brother. However, I found that I couldn’t contact you. I immediately thought that something was wrong so I went to Base Number 5. I didn’t expect that the base had really fallen.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Zheng Li couldn’t help but let out a long sigh as he said, “Fortunately, you came just in time. Otherwise, I would have fallen as well. Brother, I must say, I didn’t think that your space magic was that strong. You can actually travel a very long distance.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s nothing. But Brother, what do you plan to do now? Losing Base Number 5, isn’t that a bad thing for you?”

Zheng Li sighed and said, “It’s not only a bad thing, but it’s a very huge crime. Even if I return to the Cultivation Realm, I’m afraid I would still be punished. Now, those people should be thinking that I’m dead, and that’s not good too.”

Zhao Hai frowned and said, “Do you mean that if you return to the Cultivation Realm, then not only would you be punished, but your family as well?” Zheng Li didn’t say it like that, but Zhao Hai understood what he meant.

Zheng Li sighed and said ,”Correct.”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment, then he said, “Brother Zheng, how about this. I can return you to Seamount City and then follow you back to your family. Then I’ll send them to a base I’m planning to make in the Machine Field. There’s no need for you to go back to the Cultivation Realm. What do you think?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Zheng Li stared. He understood what Zhao Hai wanted to do. Basically, he wanted Zheng Li to betray the Cultivation Realm. But to be honest, he hasn’t thought about this situation before.

In the World of Cultivation, the position of the Cultivation Realm was the highest. Even commoners of the Cultivation Realm felt proud about this even if they were treated as farm animals.

Now that Zhao Hai wanted him to betray the Cultivation Realm, Zheng Li couldn’t help but feel somewhat awkward. Zhao Hai just looked at him in silence. He didn’t urge Zheng Li to make a decision. He believed that Zheng Li was a smart person and he knew how to make a wise choice.

If Zheng Li returned to the Cultivation Realm, then he certainly wouldn’t have any good food to eat. Therefore, he only had one road left for him. Zhao Hai also knew that Zheng Li wasn’t attracted to the Machine Field. Therefore, he can only wait for Zheng Li to make a decision. If Zheng Li doesn’t want to transfer to the Machine Field, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t persuade him otherwise.

After some time, Zheng Li looked up at Zhao Hai and said, “Alright, we’ll move to the Machine Field. This way, they wouldn’t live in fear for the future. When shall we move them?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s best if we leave right now while the news of Fabio Planet hasn’t spread far. At this time, nobody is paying attention to your family. If other people start to pay attention to your family, then things might become troublesome.

Zheng Li nodded and said, “Alright. Thank you for the trouble.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Brother Zheng, we’re not strangers. There’s no need to be polite. Let’s go.” Then he waved his hand and opened a spatial rift. Zhao Hai walked in first with Zheng Li following closely behind.

On a hill outside Seamount City, two people appeared. Zhao Hai was wearing Cultivator clothing so that he wouldn’t attract any attention. Meanwhile, Zheng Li was looking at the surroundings. This was his first time in Seamount City, so he was new to the view.

Zhao Hai released Liquid Silver and used its sword form as a flying sword and then he said, “Let’s head immediately to the transmission formation.”

Zheng Li nodded, then he took out his own flying sword and then stepped on it as they flew towards the city. Actually, identification checks were very rare in the Cultivation Realm, especially in small cities like Seamount City. If they check a person’s identity, then the other party might find it as an insult. If the person was a powerful individual, then the city wouldn’t have anyone to blame but themselves.

Zhao Hai and Zheng Li had powerful auras, so nobody dared to check them. With this, the two were able to reach Seamount City’s transmission formation with ease. When they stood on the formation, Zheng Li told the operator, “To Half Moon Planet, Riverpond City.”

The operator easily adjusted the coordinates of the formation. The operator had records of all cities within the formation’s range. They could use this record to adjust the formation’s coordinates. It can be said that the transmission formation matrix was a huge net connecting the entire Cultivation Realm.

The formation’s operator didn’t say anything and just made preparations. Then a flash of white light appeared before Zhao Hai and Zheng Li appeared in another area. The place they appeared in was much more lively than in Seamount City. The transmission formation area was also larger. White light flashed from time to time as people appeared and disappeared from the formations.

The arrival of Zhao Hai and Zheng Li didn’t attract anyone’s attention. Once the two left the transmission formation, Zhao Hai looked at Riverpond City. Then he turned to Zheng Li and said, “This Riverpond City is bigger than Seamount City. Which Sect does it belong to?”

Zheng Li looked around him, then he sighed and said, “This is under the control of the Imperial Water Sect. It’s a medium-sized sect that controls over a dozen cities including Riverpond City here in Half Moon Planet.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Zheng Li looked deeply at Riverpond City, then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Let’s go.” The two stepped on their flying swords and went outside the city.

Cultivators generally don’t use their flying swords inside a city. Flying swords could improve their speed, but it also consumed their energy. If there wasn’t an urgent matter, then Cultivators would walk instead.

However, using flying swords like Zhao Hai and Zheng Li wasn’t a rare case. At most, they would make some people look at their direction. The two quickly left Riverpond City. Outside the city were plenty of residences. These residences were usually where Cultivators lived. But these Cultivators were those who had low accomplishments. They don’t have the ability to find a place for their family inside the city, so they moved them just outside. In addition to being safe, it was also a sign of status. The closer one lived to a city, the more accomplishments a Cultivator had.

Back when Zheng Li was still a Foundation Establishment Cultivator, he was deemed too old and didn’t have potential to grow. Therefore, he never entered a sect. Naturally, his family wasn’t eligible to live in an area near the city.

Not only did his family live far from the city, they were also tasked to farm. These farms were under the Imperial Water Sect. They were workhorses for the sect.

Now, Zheng Li has become a Core Formation Cultivator, and this was done while he was in Fabio Planet. Therefore, he was able to establish his home near Riverpond City.

As soon as the two entered the residences, they heard the sound of yelling. Some people were actually fighting.

Chapter 1304: Unexpected Calamity

The sound of fighting caused Zhao Hai and Zheng Li to stare. Although Zhao Hai wasn’t from the Cultivation Realm, he stayed here for a period of time. In the Cultivation Realm, it was rare for people to fight inside a city and in the residential areas around it. This was because these areas were controlled by the sect. If people fought in these areas, then they might destroy the properties of the sect. No sect wanted this to happen.

In the past, when Helian Da went to Zhao Hai to look for trouble, they even reached an agreement to fight outside Seamount City, in an uninhabited hill. They didn’t dare cause damage to the city and the residential areas. This was because they knew that even if the Seamount Faction was a small and weak sect, they would still not let them off for damaging their property.

But now, in the residential area outside Riverpond City, some people were actually violating the Imperial Water Sect’s rules. Who has such big guts?

The two quickly flew forward. Before they reached their destination, Zheng Li’s expression changed. This was because the fight was happening close to his home.

Upon seeing the two sides who were fighting, Zhao Hai and Zheng Li couldn’t help but stare. This was because the battle was a bit out of proportion. One side only had five people while the other had much much more. The latter party was surrounding the five people and sent relentless attacks towards them.

But what’s strange about the situation was that the five-man party was actually on the winning side. Although they had been surrounded, they were defending with no problem. Every strike made by the other party would be repelled, and the attacker might even be killed.

The five people were wearing dark-blue Cultivator robes. The style of the robes was very beautiful. Although they had differing weapons in their hands, all of them held the same dark blue flag. They used these flags to attack and defend. And when shaken, these flags would cause huge waves. To their enemies, whether they were using spells or magic artifacts, they had no way to break through these waves. These waves would also swallow one or two people. Naturally, if they couldn’t escape, these people would die.

In addition to the flags, the five also had an assortment of swords and shields. Their offensive and defensive cooperation was very good. Upon analyzing the situation, Zhao Hai didn’t feel strange about what was happening. This was because the attacking side only had Foundation Establishment Experts as their strongest members. There was also a huge difference between the quality of magic artifacts between the two sides.

Although the five people also had Foundation Establishment cultivation, their magic artifacts were high-grade. This caused their attacks and defenses to be powerful. In this case, it’s no wonder that the five were able to defend.

Meanwhile, when Zheng Li saw the five people, he couldn’t help but be stunned. Compared to Zhao Hai, he had more understanding regarding Riverpond City. Governing Riverpond City was a branch hall of the Imperial Water Sect. The standard clothing of the Imperial Water Sect was the dark-blue robes. Also, the sect’s weapons were the flags used by the five people. These flags were called the Imperial Water flags. Having these weapons meant that the five people were disciples of the Imperial Water Sect. If they weren’t Inner Sect disciples, then they were certainly from the Outer Sect.

As for those besieging the Imperial Water Sect’s disciples, Zheng Li knew them as well. These people were the residents living outside Riverpond City. Zheng Li lived here for quite some time, so he knew these people. Some of these people were friends of his father. Yet these people were attacking the people of the Imperial Water Sect. What was going on? Do they want to revolt? On the lands controlled by the Imperial Water Sect, those who attack their disciples would certainly be decapitated.

Zheng Li didn’t think about it too much as he looked around. The battlefield was also strange. It wasn’t far from his home, so why didn’t his family join the attack?

Zheng Li knew that people living in the residential areas had lived there for generations. Some of them were able to cultivate, but their talent wasn’t good so they were ignored. Since they cannot join the sect, they continued living here.

Because of this, the people living in this area were very united. All of them were living at the lowest level. Since they were poor, they had developed a culture of supporting each other. Now that five disciples of the Imperial Water were attacking them, then his family should be among the attackers. So why haven’t they shown up yet?

Upon thinking about this, Zheng Li’s heart couldn’t help but sink. He ignored the fight and immediately headed towards his home. Zhao Hai saw Zheng Li’s move and paused for a moment, then he quickly followed behind.

It didn’t take long before the two arrived outside Zheng Li’s house. The Zheng Family’s house looked very ordinary. It was a worn-out stone house with no special qualities to it whatsoever.

But inside the courtyard of this residence were three coffins. The courtyard has been transformed into a mourning hall. There were two people on the ground. One of them was lying on the ground, nobody knew if he was dead or alive. The other was crying constantly.

Seeing this scene, Zheng Li’s head blanked out. He lost all capacity to think. He even stumbled when he landed on the ground. The aura of a Core Formation Cultivator had disappeared.

Zhao Hai saw Zheng Li’s expression and knew that an accident had happened to his family. He also landed on the ground and supported Zheng Li as the two entered the house.

The two walked in, then Zheng Li went to the coffins first. When he saw who were inside, he quickly fainted from grief.

The coffins were newly-made. Inside the three coffins were three corpses, one male and two female. One of the two women was an elderly lady. Her hair was white while her clothes were looking very old. Calluses could be seen on her hands. It’s clear that she had lived her life doing hard jobs.

The other woman was also somewhat old. She had a healthy set of hair while her hands were also filled with calluses. As for the man, he was dressed in Cultivator robes. However, his robes were very shabby and grey. One could see that this Cultivator died in frustration. This man’s brow looked the same as Zheng Li. It seems like this man was Zheng Li’s father.

One could see at a glance that Zheng Li’s father has been killed because of the sword wound on his throat. Zhao Hai looked at the body of Zheng Li’s father and then turned to look at the five people in the sky. He was fully certain that this had something to do with those five people.

Zheng Li was unconscious, but Zhao Hai didn’t wake him up. Instead, he took him and entered the mourning hall. White cloth were hung in the hall. But on the walls of the mourning hall, instead of the word “Settle(奠)”, what was written was the character “Enmity(仇)”.

The character for enmity was written in blood. The blood red script on the white cloth made it very striking.

Inside the mourning hall were two people wearing hempen clothes. One of them was a man about 20-years old. He was currently on the ground rapidly breathing. His complexion was flushed and he was unconscious. At the same time, Zhao Hai noticed that the man’s right sleeve was empty. And seen on the right shoulder was blood. It was clear that his arm had been ripped off.

Kneeling at the side of this man was a girl. This girl’s age was smaller at about 15 or 16. The girl was pretty, she was bound to become a beautiful woman in the future. She was currently sobbing pitifully. If this scene was on Earth, then some strange people would turn into enraged werewolves in an instant.

Zhao Hai sighed, then he waved his hand as white light fell on the young man. When the white light vanished, the breath of the young man stabilized. His face also returned to its normal color. Then the young man opened his eyes. The crying girl had also noticed that there was someone else inside the hall.

Zhao Hai sent out a gentle shake of his spiritual force to wake Zheng Li up. Upon waking up, Zheng Li quickly grasped the situation. Then he looked at the young man and the young girl. He got out of Zhao Hai’s support and then went to the young man before holding his shoulder and saying, “Little Wu, how did this happen? What is all of this about?”

Zheng Li’s younger brother was named Zheng Wi. He looked at Zheng Li seemingly unconvinced that it was Zheng Li. Seeing this, Zheng Li shook Zheng Wu’s body and said, “Little Wu, tell me. How did this happen? Why did Grandmother, Father, and Mother die?”

After being shaken by Zheng Li, Zheng Wu sobered up. Then he cried out loud. His sobbing was even more pitiful than Zheng Li’s sister.

Zheng Wu cried for some time, then he said, “Big Brother, how did you come back? Father was killed by the Imperial Water Sect. Grandmother and Mother as well. Huhuhu. Brother, you need to avenge us.”

Zheng Li’s eyes were almost spitting fire as he said, “Imperial Water Sect, you’re dead!!’ Then he flew straight towards the five Imperial Water Sect disciples.

Zhao Hai didn’t follow behind him. The five disciples were only at Foundation Establishment. With Zheng Li’s cultivation, he could deal with them easily. There was no need for Zhao Hai to go. Instead, he decided to make clear of the matter.

Zhao Hai arrived beside Zheng Wu. Then he smiled and said ,”Little Wu? I’m your Big Brother’s friend, you can call me Zhao Hai. Can you tell me what happened? Why did the Imperial Water Sect kill your father?”

Zheng Wu naturally noticed that Zhao Hai was with Zheng Li. After sobbing for some time, he answered, “Big Brother Zhao, this is because the son of the Riverpond Branch’s Hall Master has taken a liking to my little sister. He wants to make Little Sister into a cultivation furnace. Father didn’t agree. So the Hall Master sent people to kill father. They also took my arm as well as killed Grandmother and Mother.”

Chapter 1305: Inborn Charm

In the end, Zheng Wu turned out to just be a young man with no real experience. Before this, he was able to set up this mourning hall purely out of his feeling of hatred. He also wrote the character ‘enmity’. But after all of that, when he saw Zheng Li, all of it vanished.

Without a doubt, Zheng Li was the Zheng Family’s pillar of support. He was the person the family depended on for its future. Therefore, upon seeing Zheng Li, all the pressure on Zheng Wu disappeared, allowing the young man to express his grief.

As for Zheng Li’s younger sister, she had already exhausted herself crying. Even if she wanted to cry louder, she won’t be able to. Zhao Hai looked at Zheng Li’s younger sister and thought that she was indeed a beautiful girl. But after a while, Zheng Li’s sister became prettier. This was a very fatal thing to men. Even Zhao Hai who had good mental strength couldn’t help but stare at her for some time.

It was at this time that Zhao Hai’s heart felt alarmed. He quickly settled his mind and then sighed. He now knew why the son of the Hall Master wanted Zheng Li’s sister. It seems like Zheng Li’s sister was someone who was born with natural charm.

Some women were born with the ability to make their movements and actions charming and seductive.. This wasn’t something that they deliberately did, but came naturally to them. If such a woman was married to an ordinary man, then good for him. This woman would also be good at flattering others.

But there was another type of these women. At a glance, one wouldn’t be able to feel anything about them. Most people might even ignore her. However, after you notice her, your soul will be attracted. Those with weaker minds would immediately throw themselves towards that woman. If you marry that kind of woman, then that’s also good for you. Your luck is incomparable. If you were a Cultivator, then more blessings to you. Such a woman will be good for your cultivation. However, you need to remember that if you don’t have enough strength, then it’s possible that people will kill you for your woman!

Men blessed with women born with innate charm were without a doubt domineering characters. Otherwise, people will stubbornly go after them.

Zhao Hai sighed, then he turned his head towards the sky. The five Foundation Establishment disciples of the Imperial Water Sect had already been killed by Zheng Li. Others also saw Zheng Li and immediately approached him.

Zheng Li was now calm. He slowly stepped on the ground and then stored the corpses of the five disciples into his spatial equipment.

Zheng Li approached his father’s coffin and then cried loudly. At the same time, he took out the corpses of the five disciples and then took their heads as an offering to the coffin.

Those who knew Zheng Li also flew down. They looked at Zheng Li and sighed at the same time. They had been friends with Zheng Li’s family for several decades. Seeing the Zheng Family’s disaster, they also couldn’t help but feel grief.

Zhao Hai knelt beside Zheng Li and gave respects to the three coffins in front. Then he turned to Zheng Li and said, “Brother Zheng, I’m sorry for your family’s loss. But now is not the time to grief. We’re too close to Riverpond City. Once the Imperial Water Sect’s branch hall discovers the situation, they will certainly retaliate. We should make preparations.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Zheng Li quickly grasped the current situation. He stood up and looked at everyone. At the same time, those present couldn’t help but change their expression when they heard Zhao Hai. Desperation began to appear on their faces.

Zheng Li knew what these people were thinking. They had just besieged five disciples of the Imperial Water Sect. If the sect knew about this, they wouldn’t let it go.

The phrase “the law doesn’t blame the public” doesn’t apply to the Cultivation Realm. In this place, everything depended on strength. If your strength wasn’t enough, then you will be killed. Conversely, if the other party was strong enough, then they wouldn’t be blamed even if they commit genocide.

The reason these people attacked the five disciples of the Imperial Water Sect was first, the atmosphere. Second, they were frightened. If this happened to the Zheng Family today, then it might happen to them tomorrow. These people had been blinded at that time. But now that they had sobered up, they were frightened.

Zheng Li looked at his family’s friends and then looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother, what do you think we should do?”

Zhao Hai replied with a serious expression, “We kill. Let’s eliminate the Branch Hall of the Imperial Water Sect in Riverpond City first. Then we leave this place. If they’re willing to follow me, then we’ll go. If not, then they better start running now.”

Zheng Li knew that Zhao Hai wasn’t talking nonsense. Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Zheng LI knew that he was being serious. So he nodded and said, “Alright, let’s eliminate Imperial Water Sect’s Riverpond Branch first. Help me to solve the grief in my heart.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Then he looked at everyone. They didn’t lower their voices so it’s obvious that everyone heard their conversation. Everyone was confused at the two, they were even thinking that they misheard.

It was understandable, their strongest members were at Foundation Establishment. And they had no hope of progressing further in life. Moreover, they were Rogue Cultivators. It can be said that they were at the very bottom among the Cultivators.

On the other hand, the Imperial Water Sect’s Branch Hall Master was at Nascent Soul-level. To Zheng Li’s friends, those at Nascent Soul were aloof existences that they couldn’t touch. Additionally, the Riverpond City Branch had a lot of Core Formation Cultivators. And now there was Zhao Hai saying that he would extinguish the entire branch. It seems like he doesn’t place the Branch Hall in his eyes. This caused Zheng Li’s friends to think that they had misheard.

Zheng Li sighed, he knew that explaining things to them was useless. They weren’t experienced enough about the world. It was like telling a complex story to a child. So he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother, you go to Riverpond City first. I’ll deal with things here first. If they want to go, then I’ll have them prepare. If they want to leave, then I’ll let them leave as soon as possible. Also, Brother, do you have a spare spatial bag with you? Can you hand me one?”

Without delay, Zhao Hai took out a spatial bag and then handed it over to Zheng Li. Then he flew to the air and then vanished in a blink of an eye.

Seeing Zhao Hai disappear, Zheng Li sighed. Then he went to his family friends and then bowed and said, “Uncle Lu, Uncles, Little Li thanks you all. If it weren’t for you, then Wu’er and Yun’er might have been finished.”

A Foundation Establishment man waved his hand and said, “Li’er, there’s no need to say these things. Your Zheng Family and our families have been friends for generations. How could we ignore these kinds of things? Forget it, at worst, we will all die together.”

Zheng Li nodded and said, “Thank you Uncle Lu. However, Uncle Lu can feel at ease. Even if they want to kill my brother, they wouldn’t have the strength to do so. But I’m afraid that once the Riverpond Branch knows what happened, they will never let us off. Uncle Lu, now you have choices. First, you can leave Riverpond City and hide in another city. However, once the Imperial Water Sect tracks you down, you will be in danger. Your second choice is to pack your things as soon as possible and then gather here. Then everyone can come follow me later.”

Uncle Lu looked at Zheng Li in confusion, so he asked, “Come with you? Where?”

Zheng Li replied, “My Brother has some status in the Machine Field. We’ll go to the Machine Field with him. As long as we’re in the Machine Field, everyone will be safe. With the Imperial Water Sect’s strength, they wouldn’t dare go to the Machine Field to cause trouble.”

Upon hearing Zheng Li, Uncle Lu and the others didn’t say anything. With their present situation, it would be impossible for them to stay in Half-moon Planet. But if they want to leave, then they’ll have to use transmission formations. However, transmission formations were controlled by sects. Escaping meant going into the hands of the sects. And at this time, their best choice was to go to the Machine Field.

Uncle Lu looked at Zheng Li and said, “The Machine Field? But if we want to leave, then we’ll have to use transmission formations. And transmission formations are controlled by sects.”

Zheng Li nodded and said, “Uncle Lu doesn’t need to worry about that. My brother can use space magic. He can bring everyone to the Machine Field.” After he said that, explosions could be heard in the distance. It seems like Zhao Hai made his move.

When Uncle Lu and the others heard this, they knew that they needed to make a decision as soon as possible. However, this wasn’t something that Uncle Lu could decide on his own, so everyone convened and discussed what to do.

Actually, there was nothing to discuss about this matter. If they don’t go with Zheng Li, then they can only escape on their own. And if they do, then they would be courting death. Those in their right minds knew what to do.

Before long, everyone finished their discussion. Uncle Lu went to Zheng Li and said, “Alright, We’ll go with you. We’ll just die if we go on our own. But there are a lot of us, can your brother really take all of us away?”

Zheng Li nodded and said, “I’m sure. Uncle Lu, you have to pack your things and fetch your family so we can leave as soon as possible.”

Uncle Lu nodded. Then he led everyone to leave. They needed to make use of the time to pack their things. Meanwhile, Zheng Li faced the three coffins and then gave them a bow before saying, “Grandmother, Father, Mother. Your son will bring you to leave the Cultivation Realm so that you can rest in peace. Please forgive me for being impolite.” Then he covered the coffins with cloth before placing them inside the spatial bag that Zhao Hai gave him.

After tidying up, Zheng Li went to Zheng Wu and Zheng Yun. Seeing his brother and sister, Zheng Li said, “Little Wu, Little Yun, get up. We’ll be leaving this place. When Uncle Lu and the others come over, let them rest in the courtyard first. If they can’t fit inside, let them wait outside. Wait for me here, I’ll help Zhao Hai.”

Zheng Wu and Zheng Yun nodded. Zheng Yun hadn’t said anything ever since the beginning. Her lips were very dry, it seems like she couldn’t speak. She exhausted her vocal chords by crying.

Zheng Li hugged Zheng Yun. Zheng Yun also threw herself to Zheng Li as her tears unceasingly flowed down. Although the Zheng Family was a poor family, Zheng Yun was treated as the family’s treasure. Everyone in the family loved her and prepared nothing but the best for her. She also made every effort to progress, she didn’t show any spoiled attitude at all. She helped with the family work while working hard on cultivation. It was because of this that she was able to make quick progress.

However, nobody thought that she would be the reason for their family’s disaster. After Zheng Wu lost consciousness, Zheng Yun didn’t know what to do, so she could only cry. When Zheng Li arrived, he saw his younger sister cried so much that she turned mute. She couldn’t say even a few words.

Zheng Li held Zheng Yun and patted her back as he said, “Wait for Big Brother to return. Big Brother will take revenge, I’ll be back.”

Zheng Yun nodded her head, then she let go of Zheng Li. Zheng Li walked out of the room and prepared to head out. Zheng Wu also stood up. He has been heavily injured in both body and spirit. But after Zhao Hai’s treatment, he was able to recover some of his strength. At the very least, standing up wouldn’t affect his condition.

Zheng Wu looked at Zheng Li and said, “Big Brother, won’t you be in danger?”

Zheng Li looked at Zheng Wu, then he smiled faintly and said, “I’ll be fine. Your Big Brother Zhao Hai will have no problems slaughtering the entire Riverpond City. Don’t worry.”

Zheng Wu stared. He didn’t expect Zheng Li to be so confident in Zhao Hai. He knew that Riverpond City had a lot of Cultivators. Moreover, he was aware of the Branch Hall’ strength. It was also because of this knowledge that he became desperate.

Zheng Li was at Core Formation. People at Zheng Wu’s level weren’t anything in Zheng Li’s eyes. And to Zhao Hai, perhaps people like Zheng Li were nothing in his eyes.

But before Zheng Wu could say anything, a person’s shadow appeared in the air. Then Zhao Hai went to Zheng Li’s side. Seeing Zhao Hai arrive, Zheng Li couldn’t help but ask, “You’re done?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It’s been dealt with. Not only did I eliminate the Branch, I also took their treasures. This way, we can support you for a period of time while in the Machine Field. There are many pills and other things that can benefit cultivation. However, we better hurry up. I don’t think it will take long before the Imperial Water Sect get’s word about what happened here.”

Zheng Li nodded, then he turned to Zheng Wu and Zheng Yun as he said, “Alright, you two. Take your things, we’ll be leaving soon.”

Zheng Wu and Zheng Yun were now dumbfounded. They knew they didn’t misheard what Zhao Hai said. He could actually eliminate the Riverpond Branch that soon? He even snatched their treasury? How could he be that quick?

Chapter 1306: Settling Down

After Zheng Wu and Zheng Yun recovered from their shock, they quickly found themselves worshipping Zhao Hai. The two were still young and at an age where having idols to worship was very common.

Zheng Li didn’t mind the appearance of his brother and sister as he turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “We have a lot of people coming with us, can you accommodate them all?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Big Brother, feel relieved. I already made Margaret prepare ahead of time. Right, Brother, although I said that I killed the Branch Hall’s people, I actually turned them into Undead. Is that alright with you?”

Zheng Li shook his head and said, “Turning them into Undead is better. Let’s consider it as them paying reparations.” After he said this, the sound of footsteps was heard outside. Uncle Lu and the others had finished preparing and had brought their family members over.

When Uncle Lu and the others arrived at the Zheng Family’s residence, they couldn’t help but stare upon seeing Zhao Hai talking with Zheng Li. Zheng Li quickly went forward and said, “Uncle Lu, rest assured, the Imperial Water Sect’s Branch has already been dealt with by Little Hai. However, it’s possible that the Imperial Water Sect would respond soon. We need to leave quickly. Uncle Lu, please take a look and make sure that everyone is here.”

As soon as Uncle Lu heard Zheng Li, he couldn’t help but gawk. Then he turned to Zhao Hai with a doubtful look in his face. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and gave a polite salute. This made Uncle Lu and the others doubt Zhao Hai even more.

Zheng Li also noticed Uncle Lu’s expression, so he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, please show everyone the people from the Riverpond City Branch.”

Zhao Hai understood the meaning of Zheng Li, he nodded and then waved his hand. A large number of Cultivators appeared beside Zhao Hai. However, these Cultivators were all skeletons, devoid of flesh and blood. All of these skeletons were wearing the Imperial Water Sect’s dark-blue robes.

Uncle Lu and the others saw this and immediately felt thoroughly relieved. At the same time, they felt some fear towards Zhao Hai’s methods. Not only did he kill his targets, he also turned them into Undead. He wasn’t someone people could provoke.

This time, Uncle Lu didn’t hesitate anymore. He immediately counted the people present. In fact, those who participated in the fight were already prepared. After all, it’s very simple for Cultivators to move. They could just put their residence inside their spatial bags and then leave.

Rogue Cultivators were very poor, but spatial items weren’t rare in the Cultivation Realm. Even if Rogue Cultivators only had one or two artifacts, they would still have spatial items to use.

With spatial items in hand, moving was naturally very quick. Additionally, since they were poor, they didn’t own a lot of things to begin with. Most of those who should arrive had already arrived. Those who were not yet here were those who live quite far. However, it wouldn’t take long for them to arrive.

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and then said, “Brother Zheng, you lead everyone to the Machine Field first. I’ll remain here and wait for the others. After you go there, just listen to the arrangements made by the people you see.” When Zhao Hai told Zheng Li that he had Margaret arrange this matter, it was actually done. He had Margaret go to the Bone Symbol Camp and then prepared what was needed. As long as Zheng Li and the others arrive, the people from the Bone Symbol Camp will immediately receive them and give them the basic things they would need.

This operation would not experience any problems. After all, Zhao Hai had become the pride of the Bone Symbol Camp. His status wasn’t any worse than Desbarres. Moreover, his relationship with Tie Sheng and Tao Wang was very good. Then there was Margaret. The Bone Symbol Camp was naturally happy to help Zhao Hai.

When Zheng Li heard Zhao Hai, he nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll go there now.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he waved his hand and opened a spatial rift beside him. This rift wasn’t very big, just enough for two people to enter at the same time. Zheng Li cupped his fist towards Zhao Hai, then he entered the spatial rift.

The spatial passage wasn’t very long. It only took a few steps before Zheng Li came out on the other side. Standing outside the passage was a very pretty woman. This woman was wearing mage robes. From the atmosphere, it was clear that she has been waiting for him. The woman immediately said, “Margaret has seen Brother Zheng Li.”

Zheng Li already guessed Margaret’s status. He immediately returned the greeting, “I’ve seen sister-in-law. This time, I’ll have to trouble you.”

Margaret smiled faintly and said, “Big Brother Zheng is too polite. You and Brother Hai are Brothers. It’s normal to offer help at this time. This is Ashley Family’s Bone Symbol Camp. Your living arrangements have already been arranged. This is the camp that Brother Hai started in. However, you’ll only reside here temporarily. You’ll live in a better place in the future. Is Brother Zheng Li alright with this?”

Zheng Li nodded and said, “Then I’ll have to ask Sister-in-law to help us arrange everything.” At this time, Tie Sheng and Tao Wang also arrived and exchanged greetings with Zheng LI. Then Uncle Lu and the others began walking out of the spatial rift.

Once Uncle Lu and the others arrived, they were immediately welcomed by the Bone Symbol Camp into the large building and then gave them their dwellings. The camp also helped Uncle Lu and the others to get familiar with their new environment. Their hospitality was very good.

The Bone Symbol Camp were also very eager to please the people from the Cultivation Realm. With Uncle Lu and the others present, the Bone Symbol Camp’s strength would increase.

One must know that although Uncle Lu and the others weren’t looked highly upon in the Cultivation Realm, they were still Cultivators in the end. They were comparatively stronger than most Mages, Warriors, and Mechs. If they were integrated into the Bone Symbol Camp, then the camp’s strength would be boosted. Therefore, Tie Sheng and Tao Wang were attaching great importance towards Uncle Lu’s group.

Zheng Li watched the camp’s hospitality as they settled Uncle Lu and the others. It must be said that the Bone Symbol Camp truly had plenty of rooms. Moreover, compared to the outer residences of Riverpond City, the camp’s environment was vastly different. There were a lot of things that they needed to get used to. Uncle Lu and the others suddenly discovered that their own lifestyle had improved. Their family members didn’t need to work hard everyday anymore. They didn’t even need to cook their food and wash their clothes, they had robots to take care of it. If they want, they can just sleep all day.

This arrangement caused them to be beyond satisfied. At the same time, after getting in contact with the members of the camp, they naturally became aware of Zhao Hai’s reputation in the Machine Field. Most importantly, they knew Zhao Hai’s influence in the Bone Symbol Camp. It didn’t take long before they developed a new reverence towards Zhao Hai.

The Rogue Cultivators that participated in attacking the Imperial Water Sect numbered about 300 people. Whether they were injured or killed, their family members have been moved to the Bone Symbol Camp. More than a thousand people appeared in the Bone Symbol Camp. But even with this, the camp was still able to accommodate them well.

The Bone Symbol Camp’s region was originally very big, and they also had a lot of available rooms. Although the camp had a lot of Warriors and Mages, they don’t actually live in the camp’s main building. This was because they have their own villas on another part of the island. Most people from the Bone Symbol Camp would generally want to live in those villas. Therefore, the large building of the Bone Symbol Camp was fairly empty. Therefore, there were no issues in arranging places for Uncle Lu and the others to live in.

After everyone had entered the spatial passage, Zhao Hai looked at Zheng Wu and Zheng Yun, then he smiled and said, “Everyone has gone in, you should go as well. I reckon the Imperial Water Sect already knew about what happened. But it doesn’t matter. After you go to the Machine Field, you can also practice. When you gain enough strength, you can come back and look for revenge.”

Zheng Wu and Zheng Yun were now looking at Zhao Hai as their idol. Zhao Hai was able to appease their enmity as well as save a large number of people. This caused them to worship him. Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the two nodded immediately and then walked towards the spatial rift.

Before long, the two arrived at the Bone Symbol Camp. Zhao Hai also went in and greeted Tie Sheng and Tao Wang. Then he returned to the Six Realms Battlefield.

After all, his focus right now was still the Six Realms Battlefield. He can’t stay outside for too long. Zheng Li also didn’t oppose it. He went to bury his parents and grandmother first then he helped the Bone Symbol Camp communicate with Uncle Gu and the others so that they could get used to life in the Machine Field as soon as possible.

The lifestyle of the Machine Field varies greatly from the Cultivation Realm. In the Cultivation Realm, people rarely used robots and machines. Everyone was dedicated to cultivating. Those who can’t cultivate would go out and farm the fields. Moreover, herbs in the Cultivation Realm weren’t taken care of by machines. This was because the plants were very expensive. It would be troublesome if a machine malfunctions and destroys everything. Therefore, the people from the Cultivation Realm employed old methods to harvest plants.

Additionally, electricity hasn’t spread out in the Cultivation Realm. Generally, only huge cities would have electricity. In this case, using computers or robots was impossible. Therefore, the lifestyle of the Cultivation Realm was relatively more primitive. This was especially true for commoners like the families of Uncle Lu and the others.

But in the Machine Field, the lives of everyone were aided by all kinds of machines. In every home were electric appliances and each family would have at least one or two robots. This was vastly different to the Cultivation Realm. Now that Uncle Lu and the others were going to live in the Machine Field from now on, then they would need to get used to using these machines. This way, their integration to the Machine Field would be smooth.

And since it was because of the Zheng Family that Uncle Lu and the others had to transfer, Zheng Li took upon himself to aid Uncle Lu and the others at all steps going forward. It was also good that the Bone Symbol Camp took care of them very well. Slowly, Uncle Lu and the others were able to be accustomed to living in the Machine Field and the Bone Symbol Camp.

Chapter 1307: Transforming Yalei 2

Yuan was currently standing on the fort walls along with Wu Yang, Xiong Li, and Zhao Hai’s other brothers. Although Xiong Li and the others were newcomers, their strength and weapons allowed them to contend with Yuan when they teamed up. This kind of strength made Yuan see them as important people.

Naturally, this was only part of the reason why. The main reason was because of Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was very strong. Additionally, he was capable of refining weapons for everyone. And with Xiong Li and the others being his brothers, it was normal for Yuan to see them as important.

At this point, Yuan was already aware that Zhao Hai had sworn brotherhood with Xiong Li and the others. Moreover, Yuan was able to learn more about Zhao Hai from them. Their testimonies made Yuan and the others admire Zhao Hai even more.

Wu Yang, who was beside Yuan, was talking with Li Kuangren. Then suddenly he said, “Old Li, are you telling the truth? Does Little Hai have a lot of good wine?”

Li Kuangren nodded and said, “Of course. Why would I lie? If you don’t believe me, ask Xiong Li and the others. Little Hai’s wine is very delicious. Not only that, it’s also beneficial for cultivation. It’s very good.”

Wu Yang made a ‘tian’ ‘tian’ sound with his mouth as he said, “Now I want to taste it.”

Li Kuangren looked at Wu Yang, then he smiled and said, “You won’t regret it.”

As they were speaking, Yuan suddenly looked at his wrist computer. Then his expression changed as he turned to Xiong Li and said, “Has Little Hai always been inside the cave residence?”

As soon as they heard Yuan’s question, Xiong Li and the others couldn’t help but feel awkward. They had been getting along well with Yuan these days, so they didn’t want to deceive him. Xiong Li and the others were very certain that Zhao Hai wasn’t in the cave residence, that place was just a cover.

Upon seeing the strange expression on their faces, Yuan knew that there were secrets involved. So he said, “Let’s go into a private room.” Then the group relocated to a private room and then sat down. Yuan looked at Xiong Li and the others and said, “So what’s the matter?”

Xiong Li looked at Yuan, then he asked, “How did Captain know that something’s wrong?”

Yuan couldn’t help but smile bitterly as he said, “Take a look.” Then he opened his wrist computer and released a projection. Shown was a string of words that relays information. The information said that Zhao Hai has been spotted in Dark Demon Planet along with a large number of people from the Cultivation Realm. These people were now living inside the Bone Symbol Camp.

When they read this information, Xiong Li and the others couldn’t help but laugh. Then Li Kuangren said, “This kid, if he wants to head out, then at least he should have sneaked in some wine.”

Then as Li Kuangren said this, Zhao Hai’s voice was heard, “Fourth Brother, I’ve been busy the past few days. How could I find time to give you some wine?”

Everyone stared, then they all turned to see Zhao Hai standing in the room smiling at them. Xiong Li and the others immediately approached him as Yuan and Wu Yang looked at each other. Amazement could be seen in each others’ eyes. This was because they hadn’t discovered Zhao Hai entering the room.

Xiong Li looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, why are you at the Bone Symbol Camp? What happened?”

Zhao Hai didn’t immediately reply, instead he turned to Yuan and said, “Captain, I apologize for hiding the truth from you. Actually, my space magic allows me to come in and out of the Six Realms Battlefield whenever I want.”

Yuan nodded and said, “So what happened?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “It’s not a big deal. During my break, I tried to contact a friend in Fabio Planet. However, I cannot get ahold of him. Thinking of how dangerous the planet was, I decided to check it out. But when I arrived, I discovered that the entire base had been destroyed. So I saved him and then accompanied him back to his family. But who knew that something else happened.” Then he continued on to describe the latter events.

As Zhao Hai spoke, Yuan’s emotions got more elevated. Zheng Li’s situation resembled his own. But Yuan relied on himself to get out of trouble while Zheng Li was fortunate enough to have some people take revenge for him and then send him to the Machine Field.

After some time, Yuan calmed down, he nodded and said, “You did the right thing. If you didn’t, then the entire Zheng Family would die as well as the families of those involved. However, now that you have escaped, those living outside Riverpond City will be unlucky.”

“What’s wrong with them?”, Zhao Hai asked. “Is the Imperial Water Sect that unreasonable?”

Yuan sneered and said, “That unreasonable? Little Hai, you’re too naive. There’s no such thing as reason in the Cultivation Realm. If you count on them being reasonable, then you might as well hang yourself. Alright, let’s not talk about this. What happened to my weapon? If you didn’t do well, then you’ll have to answer to me kid.”

Zhao Hai smiled. Then he turned his hand, taking out a sledgehammer. Then he handed the sledgehammer to Yuan and said, “Captain, try this out.”

Yuan stared, then he took the sledgehammer and then went out of the room. Then he flew up and went outside the fort to make an attack. A huge ‘boom’ was heard. Such a loud sound couldn’t be hidden from the entire fort. Everyone immediately ran out holding their weapons. They all thought that they were under attack.

But after Zhao Hai and the others explained the situation, everyone calmed down. At this time, Yuan already returned from outside. He couldn’t help but look at his sledgehammer for a while before putting it away. Then he laughed and said, “Little Hai, nice job. With this weapon, even Core Formation Cultivators couldn’t win against me.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s good that you like it, Captain. I’ll make sure to finish everyone’s weapon as soon as I can.”

Yuan nodded, then he patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said ,”Thanks for the trouble, Little Hai. These weapons are too important to us. These past few days, the Sprites had been causing too much trouble. They would come over and provoke us once in a while. You have to finish the weapons quickly.”

Zhao Hai raised his eyebrows and said, “The Sprites? Are they courting death? Alright, I’ll head back now. I’ll finish everyone’s weapons as soon as I can.” Yuan nodded. Then Zhao Hai’s body quickly vanished.

What Yuan didn’t know was that Zhao Hai had already finished all the weapons. However, it would be awkward for him to take them all at the same time.

Zhao Hai returned to the Space and then looked at the situation outside Riverpond City. He wanted to see if the Imperial Water Sect was just like what Yuan said.

At this time, Zhao Hai discovered that his understanding of the Cultivation Realm was still too far from Yuan’s. The scene outside Riverpond City was a giant slaughter. An uncountable amount of Rogue Cultivators were killed.

Seeing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but clench his teeth in hatred. However, he couldn’t go to Riverpond City right now. This was because he discovered that there were a lot of experts present. Even the Sect Master of the Imperial Water Sect personally arrived.

Zhao Hai underestimated the amount of trouble that was caused by the event. Imperial Water Sect was a medium-grade sect. They didn’t have a lot of cities under their control. Up to now, they only controlled a dozen cities and Riverpond City was one of their best cities. But then, they suddenly received news that their Riverpond City Branch had been destroyed. This was such a great event. So how could the Imperial Water Sect not come over and investigate?

They scoured the entire city. But they couldn’t understand how small Rogue Cultivators living outside the city were able to eliminate an entire branch of the sect. Additionally, Zheng Li and the others were able to run away. All involved were gone. The Imperial Water Sect felt suffocated and there was nobody they could direct this hatred. In the end, bad luck descended upon the Rogue Cultivators outside Riverpond City.

After looking at the situation for some time, Zhao Hai shifted his attention to the Bone Symbol Camp. Although the people outside Riverpond City were killed, these people didn’t have anything to do with him. He wasn’t responsible for their lives. Therefore, he didn’t think too much about this matter. This matter made him understand more about the World of Cultivation.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t let the Imperial Water Sect off. As long as the sect’s troops scatter, he would teach the sect a lesson. In any case, now that he has offended the sect, he might as well make them expend some energy.

The Bone Symbol Camp turned back to normal. Uncle Lu and the others had been settled down. At the same time, the Bone Symbol Camp was very enthusiastic. Zhao Hai felt relief upon seeing this.

Margaret was currently in the Bone Symbol Camp. With her presence there, Uncle Lu and the others were be able to smoothly integrate to the Machine Field as soon as possible.

Actually, Zhao Hai didn’t want Uncle Lu and the others to stay in the Bone Symbol Camp for a long time. Once Yalei 2 has been prepared, he would send them there.

Upon thinking of this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but shift the screen’s display to Yalei 2. Seeing Zhao Hai looking at the planet, Laura smiled and said, “Brother Hai doesn’t need to worry about this. I already asked Cai’er to place one of her branches in Yalei 2. Also, we installed the heart of earth fire in order to increase the planet’s temperature and melt the ice caps.”

Zao Hai nodded, “Alright, you can take your time. Later on, try separating some roots of the Hundred Spirits Tree and replant them into the planet to make the spiritual density thicker.”

Laura knit her brows and said, “Brother Hai, I believe separating the Hundred Spirit Tree’s root isn’t a good idea. You should know that the roots are currently supplying the Space, and the Space is our foundation. Meanwhile, Yalei 2 is just an outside base. It’s not good if something goes wrong. I think it’s better if we transplant Elven Trees there. Although it’s not as good, they can still improve the spiritual density of the planet. What do you think?”

Chapter 1308: The Sprites Are On The Move

Upon hearing Laura, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright. Then I’ll leave it to you. After everything is prepared, we’ll take Uncle Lu and the others to the planet. Although it’s only our decoy base, it’s precisely because of this that we need to build it well so that others would think that it is our real base.”

Laura nodded and said, “Alright, leave it to me. You don’t have to worry. Right, Brother Hai, we have things to deal with about the Lower Realm. How about you take a look?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “I think we should delegate the matters of the Lower Realm to other people. This will help us to process the Space’s matters better. After all, dealing with these things is unsuitable with our present status.”

Laura nodded. She didn’t oppose it. Now that the Space has leveled up to this degree, there’s nothing in the Lower Realms that could help it. Moreover, the planets currently inside the Space were now much bigger than the lower realms. It can be said that the Lower Realm was now useless for the Space. Of course, this didn’t include the Underworld.

The Underworld’s situation was special. As long as it had the big heart, the Underworld would continue to develop. Zhao Hai’s heart has also been replaced by the heart in the Underworld. This was the reason why Zhao Hai’s strength was able to increase so fast.

The Underworld couldn’t be left all alone. However, with there being people that could help him, Zhao Hai doesn’t need to be worried. As for other small things, to be honest, Zhao Hai doesn’t really want to care.

After dealing with his issue, Zhao Hai went back to the soft gold mine to take more Demons for the Space. Then he took a few days to rest inside the Space.

Five days later, Margaret returned to the Space. At this point, Zheng Li and the others had been able to properly settle down in the Bone Symbol Camp. Additionally, Zheng Li and the others had joined the camp temporarily. Zhao Hai also gave the Riverpond Branch’s pills and magic artifacts to Zheng Li so that he could give it to Uncle Lu and the others.

This action made Uncle Lu and the others weep in gratitude. They were Rogue Cultivators with no money to buy pills or magic artifacts. Now that they had these things, their cultivation would gain a big boost. Their fighting strength would certainly increase.

Naturally, the biggest problem with being in the Machine Field was that the spiritual density was less than in the Cultivation Realm. This would affect Uncle Lu and the others’ cultivation greatly. But with the pills, this was no longer an issue. Moreover, they were also able to survive. And with the environment of the Bone Symbol Camp, they had nothing to complain about.

Despite being Rogue Cultivators, Uncle Lu and the others could still enter Sects. However, it wasn’t very easy for Rogue Cultivators to enter a sect. People like Zheng Li who were able to reach Core Formation were already very lucky. And the reason why Zheng Li was able to reach Core Formation was because he went to Fabio Planet. Fabio Planet was a very dangerous place. If it weren’t for Zheng Li’s luck, then he wouldn’t have survived long enough to reach Core Formation. And if it weren’t for Zhao Hai, then Zheng Li might have perished from the Bug attack.

Therefore, if a Rogue Cultivator wanted to return to the sect, then it would be very difficult. A lot of Rogue Cultivators were still unable to enter a Sect for generations. In the end, they had to fight for their own survival.

Because of these reasons, Uncle Lu and the others weren’t so opposed to moving away from the Cultivation Realm. At the same time, this allows them to smoothly integrate into the Bone Symbol Camp.

Zhao Hai was glad to see this happening. Meanwhile, he was observing Riverpond City for the last 5 days. The Imperial Water Sect was attaching great importance to the recent matter. The Patriarch personally took charge and then checked all avenues to see how the Branch Hall was eliminated.

However, they weren’t able to see the entire picture. The only thing they knew was that there were two people who came from Seamount City, one was Zheng Li while the other was an unknown person.

But after the Imperial Water Sect checked on Zheng Li, they discovered that he was supposed to have died on Fabio Planet. The Imperial Water Sect became puzzled about this. Then they began to suspect that the attackers were using false appearances in order to stage their attack. The Sect began to feel afraid that this attack was targeted on the entire sect itself.

With the Imperial Water Sect being suspicious, Zhao Hai didn’t dare take the matter lightly. He wasn’t able to find an opportunity to make an attack. However, he wasn’t in a hurry so he waited.

Today, Zhao Hai woke up and then had breakfast. After eating, he left the Space and returned to the fort. The people in the fort had also finished eating and were now chatting with each other.

It must be said that normal life in the fort was very idle. There wasn’t much to do in the fort. Their obligation was just to defend the area and hunt once in a while.

However, they wouldn’t hunt very often due to how dangerous the battlefield was. Once they go hunting, they would rest for a long time in order to readjust their condition.

After seeing Zhao Hai come out, everyone immediately approached him and then gave him a warm greeting. It didn’t take long before they asked him about the weapons.

Zhao Hai looked at everyone and then he smiled faintly and said, “Everyone must have been anxious. I have already prepared the weapons. Please come get them.” When they heard Zhao Hai, they all cheered. Then they surrounded him and then came one by one to get their weapons.

All those who got their weapons immediately went out and tested them. Naturally, the results were very satisfactory. The weapons made by the processing machine had always been high-quality goods.

After everyone received their weapons, almost nobody was left in the fort. After one hour, people began to return one by one. Everyone expressed their happiness. The weapons that Zhao Hai made satisfied their needs. They were convenient to use and were powerful.

Once everyone had returned, they all invited Zhao Hai to drink. Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t decline. Yuan was also very happy. A lot of liquor has been taken out as everyone drank themselves dizzy.

The next morning, Zhao Hai got up early and went to the cafeteria to have breakfast. In the common hall, everyone’s expressions were miserable. It was clear that they suffered severe hangovers.

After breakfast, everyone’s situation got better. Then everyone gathered on the fort walls and looked at the situation outside. The scenery outside the fort wasn’t very beautiful. However, all of them want to hunt right now, so all of them want to head out.

Yuan was also aware of everyone’s thoughts, but didn’t say anything. And since he didn’t say anything, nobody said anything. After all, this place was Yuan’s territory.

Zhao Hai stood beside Yuan and then said, “Captain, didn’t you say that the Sprites had been provoking us for some time? Do you think we should teach them a lesson? Let them behave for a while?”

As soon as everyone heard Zhao Hai, they all looked at Yuan with shining eyes. Seeing everyone looking at him with expectation, Yuan sighed and said, ”You think I don’t want to attack the Sprites? However, now is not the time. The Sprites had been provoking us continuously, but we haven’t heard of any large-scale attack. It’s clear that they are waiting for us to retaliate and then ambush us. I don’t want this to happen. Therefore, I decided to stay put. Little Hai, I’ll have to trouble you to scout ahead. Only after we get a clear picture of the situation could we act.”

Zhao Hai nodded and admired Yuan’s decision. Naturally, he knew that the Sprites were waiting to ambush them outside. And they had a lot of people. Although the Space hadn’t completely mapped out the entire Six Realms battlefield, the Machine Field’s partially controlled territory as well as the core battlefield had already been mapped. It was because of this that Zhao Hai knew very well that a lot of Sprites were waiting to ambush them outside.

The Sprites had gathered about 1,000 people this time. They waited not far away while sending small teams to attack the Lock Mountain Range in order to lure some of them to come out. Once the pursuers went out of bounds, then they would proceed to ambush them.

It seems like the Sprites had been thinking about this for a long time. A group of 1000 people was very rare in the Six Realms Battlefield. It was almost equal to two realms worth of large troops battling all out in the core battlefield.

Zhao Hai was clear about the situation because he has seen it for himself. Meanwhile, Yuan was able to deduce it through the reports given, which was an amazing feat.

Zhao Hai left the fort and then slowly progressed towards the Sprites’ ambush location. Although he was aware of the Sprite’s position, he still had to go there in order to see the exact situation of the terrain. This way, the Machine Field would be able to deal with them better.

Zhao Hai was very careful this time so he wasn’t discovered by the Sprites. He drew a clear map of where the Sprites were and also the places where they weren’t in. Then he returned to the camp.

The technology of the Machine Field was very advanced. At this point, the Machine Field’s computer had a lot of built-in functions. For example, it could record Zhao Hai’s merit. At the same time, being a high-level computer, not only could it display images, it could also project three-dimensional recordings.

Most computers don’t have this function. Only military computers like what Zhao Hai and the others used have this ability. It was basically a virtual sand table. However, compared to a normal sand table, it was more convenient to use.

The map that Zhao Hai made was recorded in three-dimensions. Although the computer could map the entire terrain in 3D, the locations of the enemies still needed Zhao Hai’s input to be included.

This wasn’t easy work. The Sprites weren’t weak, and they also have their summons as well as formidable spiritual force. Being stealthy enough to not be discovered by them was very hard.

There’s also the Sprite Race’s ability to communicate with any non-living thing. Even if their spiritual force didn’t sense you, any old tree or rock could still inform the Sprites of your location.

Zhao Hai determined the position of the Sprites as well as their numbers. After recording everything properly, Zhao Hai felt satisfied.

Zhao Hai didn’t immediately return to the camp and instead detoured to the Space. Only after resting for some time did he return to the fort.

Naturally, Yuan and the others wouldn’t spend all the time on the wall to wait for him to come back. Some people had returned to their rooms to practice while some chatted with each other. The fort returned to its peaceful state.

Seeing that Zhao Hai had come back, Yuan immediately called everyone to the fort’s meeting room. When everyone was present, Yuan waved towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai nodded and then appeared in front of everyone and then opened his computer to release the projection. Displayed was a very clear depiction of the terrain as well as red dots on the mamp.

Zhao Hai doesn’t need to explain much since everything was clearly shown. Zhao Hai gestured towards the map and said, “This is the Sprites’ ambush region. I discovered that they had 960 people altogether. 60 of them are at Nascent Soul-level while the remaining are all at Core Formation. Every day, they would send out 30 to 50 people to poke the mountain range. Their goal is to provoke us and then retreat towards the Sprite Race’s semi-controlled territory. Because of this, we wouldn’t suspect anything and would end up in their ambush.”

Upon seeing this, Yuan couldn’t help but frown as he said, “What are the Sprites doing? Why did they send so many people? Are they completely throwing face away in order to kill us?” Everyone in the hall was silent. Although they experienced constant conflicts in the Six Realms Battlefield, these were all small-scale conflicts. Large-scale fights were incredibly rare. The actions of the Sprites this time were surprising.

Yuan turned silent for some time, then he said, “The decision for this matter is beyond my control. Report this matter to the higher-ups and let them decide. Meanwhile, immediately inform everyone in the mountain range to enter stage 1 alert level. No matter what kind of provocation the Sprites make, they aren’t allowed to fight. They shouldn’t show any signs of preparation for battle.”

Everyone complied and then went on to settle their responsibilities. After everyone left, Yuan’s brows wrinkled. Then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, why do you think the Sprites are doing this? Do they want to conquer the Machine Field? Isn’t this too ambitious for them? This group isn’t a small number. If both of us really fight, the other realms would be able to get benefits for cheap. They shouldn’t be this foolish.”

Zhao Hai was also frowning, then he said, “The Sprites’ action is indeed very confusing. However, I don’t think they want an all-out war against us. If they did, then they wouldn’t have resorted to ambushes. They must have come this time to strike an important target. In order to ensure their success, they sent a lot of people.”

Chapter 1309: Deploying Troops

Yuan frowned and said, “Target? But if the Sprites are looking for a target, then who might it be?”

Then as he said this, Yuan’s eyes suddenly shone. He turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, you mean their targets are..” Then he referred to himself and then towards Liu Zhen. This was because the Sprites staged an ambush against them in the past. In other words, the two were in danger.

Zhao Hai understood what Yuan wanted to say, he nodded and said, “That’s one of the possibilities. Captain, you and Captain Liu Zhen are two of our best fighters. You are also the most threatening people for the other realms. The territory of the Sprites is just right next to us. Moreover, the two of you have caused no small damage to the Sprites. A lot of Sprites want the both of you dead. As long as you two aren’t dealt with, the Sprites wouldn’t be able to live in peace.”

After he spoke this, Zhao Hai stopped for a moment before continuing, “However, with how much they regard the two of you, the Sprites certainly know that you won’t be going out of the mountain range soon. However, they still kept sending people to provoke us. This means that they want the two of you to counter. As long as you lead your people out, you will be going straight into their hands. But obviously, the Sprites have been underestimating you.”

Yuan laughed and said, “Correct. They underestimated me. They think that this Yuan is just a musclehead. They didn’t know that I wouldn’t have survived for so long if I wasn’t able to think for myself. I think we need to make them suffer this time.”

Zhao Hai didn’t oppose Yuan’s opinion. Since the Sprites wanted a fight, then the Machine Field would comply. They needed to be hurt so bad that the Sprites would behave.

But as the matter stands, this would forge an irresolvable feud between the Sprites and the Machine Field. However, almost all six realms in the World of Cultivation were enemies. Elevating how much they hate each other wasn’t a big deal.

Zhao Hai looked at Yuan and said ,”Captain, what do you plan to do?”

Yuan smiled and said, “The Machine FIeld has the most practitioners among all of the six realms. This is because compared to the methods of the other realms, the Machine Field’s cultivation methods have less limitations. Therefore, we have the most people in the Six Realms Battlefield. This is the reason why the other realms couldn’t push us back. Now that the Sprites decided to take a poke at us, we better return their hospitality. With our numbers we can surround the Sprites instead. Even if we can’t wipe them out, they would still feel pain.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Good. Let’s make the other realms understand that the Machine Field cannot be bullied. I think the Sprites want to make the Lock Mountain Range return to what it was before. They plan to make us lose our semi-controlled territory so that they can take advantage of us and get more resources.

Yuan nodded, “If those fellows want to pressure the Machine Field, then they would first pressure our hold in the Six Realms Battlefield. Naturally, we cannot make them succeed. Therefore, we need to hit them ruthlessly this time.”

Zhao Hai agreed. Yuan continued, “Little Hai, you have to take a good rest. We will need your strength. Besides stopping their strong experts, we also need your undead to block their summons.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he gave Yuan a salute before turning around and leaving. Yuan immediately arranged people to send word to the other forts. He also sent requests to prepare to battle the army of Sprites.

Defending a place like the Lock Mountain Range couldn’t be done without a unified chain of command. The Machine Field doesn’t only have experts who have Core Formation strength. The realm also had Mages and Warriors that reached Nascent Soul-level. The strength of these people couldn’t be underestimated. All of these people in addition to magic cannons and other devices allowed the Machine Field to safely defend their territory.

This time, since the Sprites made a huge move, the commanders needed to be unified. With Yuan’s status, he couldn’t take command of this huge operation. Therefore, more people have to cooperate with him.

Moving large numbers of people couldn’t be done in a short time. Moreover, this needed to be done in a way where the Sprites wouldn’t be able to sense it. Yuan and the others also strengthened the defensive capability of the Lock Mountain Range. As the Sprites continued their small attacks, they discovered that the defense of the mountain range was getting stronger and stronger. And because of this, they didn’t suspect that the Machine Field was planning to surround them.

Zhao Hai has been very relaxed during these days. Although he was strong, his time in the Six Realms Battlefield was still too short. He had yet to establish his prestige. Additionally, he still hasn’t grasped the situation with the battlefield. Naturally, he wasn’t assigned important work. What he needed to do was rest and prepare himself for the battle since he would be facing the main force.

This time, the Sprites seems to have made some effort and managed to deploy 60 Nascent Soul Experts. The Machine Field naturally competed with this amount. Within a short time, the mountain range was able to amass ten thousand people. They were divided into ten teams with each team consisting of 1000 people. Then these teams proceeded to position themselves to surround the Sprites.

And in each team were two Nascent Soul-level experts. Although there were only 20 Nascent Soul-level experts all-in-all, this was everything that the Machine Field could muster up for this operation. Although the Machine Field still had more Nascent Soul-level experts, these people needed to remain so that the other realms wouldn’t use this opportunity to attack the Mountain Range.

The reassignment of people as well as positioning them required time. Meanwhile, Yuan and the others haven’t moved at all. This was because they needed to stay as bait. This would make the Sprites suspect nothing.

Yuan also led the others out for a few times in order to fight the Sprites. But after seeing that they couldn’t get any advantages, the Sprites immediately retreated, not giving Yuan the chance to fight seriously. Naturally, Yuan acted like he was enraged by this. He looked as if he was going to chase the Sprites.

Yuan’s performance made the Sprites think that everything was going normally. Therefore, the frequency of their attacks increased while they didn’t move from their original position.

It must be said that picking a place for ambush wasn’t easy. Moreover, the Sprites knew that if they changed places constantly, then they would risk being discovered by the Machine Field and lose the significance of their ambush. They also knew that it was impossible for their 1000-people team to attack the Lock Mountain Range.

Lock Mountain Range was essentially 10 defensive lines that were manned all year round. As for where Yuan’s territory was, it was only on the first defensive line. Behind it were even more forts. As long as Yuan’s camp gets into trouble, the forts behind them would certainly help and send reinforcements to strengthen the defense. Wanting to attack the Lock Mountain Range with only 1000 people was impossible. The Machine Field’s people weren’t soft eggs that could be easily defeated.

Although the Sprites looked down on the strength of the Machine Field, they didn’t doubt their ability. The Machine Field was the most ruthless among the six realms.

Zhao Hai didn’t make a single move at this time. Yuan also urged him to stay put. If Zhao Hai vanished, then the Sprites would find out right away. Therefore, Zhao Hai announced that he was going to close up inside his cave residence.

Whether the news entered the ears of the Sprites or not, Yuan still made an excuse. This way, Zhao Hai can play the role of a rogue soldier.

Zhao Hai hasn’t been idling these past few days either. He has been monitoring the Sprites’ situation while inside the Space. The Sprites didn’t change their place of ambush. But Zhao Hai discovered that the Sprites had turned the trees, stones, and even the air near the ambush area into their spirits. This also allowed them to expand their area of battle.

However, this has no effect on the operation of the Machine Field. At this point, the encirclement was about to be done. As soon as the encirclement is finished, Yuan would pursue the Sprites and enter their ambush area. Then the battle would begin.

It can be said that Yuan was the bait to attract the Sprites. The Sprites expected to eat them but would instead be trapped in a bigger net created by the Machine Field.

When the large net was set-up, Yuan would immediately become a bomb that exploded. Together with the encirclement outside, two groups would join forces in order to deal with the Sprites in one stroke.

Yuan’s team held confidence going into this fight. The reason for their confidence was their weapons. Their weapons were made by Zhao Hai. Back when they tested their weapons, they found that its power had improved. And in the small skirmishes with the Sprites, they discovered that the effects of their weapons were extremely powerful. Not only is the spiritual qi requirement less, its attacking strength has also increased – especially in close combat. In the past, Yuan would expend a lot of energy in order to deal with a spirit summon. But with his new weapon, as long as he hit the summon a few times, then the summon would be destroyed. And this was the defensively strong summons like the tree spirits and the stone spirits. As for wind spirits, all of them were destroyed in one attack. This showed how strong Zhao Hai’s weapons were!

Chapter 1310: Golden Sprite Murdoch

Zhao Hai was currently standing on top of a wall alongside Yuan. But this time, they weren’t at Yuan’s fort. Instead, they were in another fort. This was the fort that had been constantly harassed by the Sprites.

Zhao Hai appeared this time because the Machine Field’s action against the Sprites was about to begin. The giant net around the Sprites has been formed. The only thing left to do was for Yuan to be the bait.

Along with Yuan were 100 people. These 100 people were all from Yuan and Liu Zhen’s camp. These were the people who had their weapons made by Zhao Hai. They were now waiting for the Sprites to come provoke them. As long as the Sprites come, they would immediately charge out and then enter their ambush region. Once the Sprites bite the bait, the encirclement would begin to move.

The Sprites didn’t disappoint Zhao Hai and the others. Right when the clock struck 9 am, the Sprites appeared. The reason why Zhao Hai and the others were prepared was because the actions of the Sprites were very regular. They would only attack about a dozen forts in a region at 9 am then they would retreat immediately.

This pattern has been noticed by Yuan and the others but they pretended to not know about it. However, the Sprites might also be doing this intentionally. They wanted Yuan and the others to discover the pattern so that they would wait for them in time. And then when they retreat, Yuan would lead his team to pursue.

Sure enough, as soon as the Sprites appeared, Yuan was already waiting for them. The Sprites also discovered Zhao Hai. However, without saying a word they turned around and ran.

Yuan angrily said, “Pursue! Kill those bastards!” Then as he said that, he flew and chased the Sprites. Zhao Hai and the others also flew closely behind.

At this point, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but admire Yuan. His movement as well as expression was flawless. You couldn’t see that he was just acting. Even the mood in his voice was perfect.

The Sprites discovered that Yuan was different today. In the past, Yuan would still pursue them, but not to this extent. But this time, it seems like Yuan was intent on pursuing them to the depths of hell. And this was what the Sprites wanted.

The chase continued on until they had left the partially controlled territory of the Machine Field. Once this happened, Zhao Hai and the others began to be careful. They all took out their weapons because they knew that they would soon enter the Sprites’ ambush region.

Yuan was still roaring with anger as he kept chasing behind the Sprites. But Zhao Hai could also notice that Yuan was looking at his left and right sides from time to time as if paying attention to the surroundings.

Before long, Zhao Hai and the others entered the ambush area. The moment they went in, the dense forest around them immediately became tree spirits and moved forward.

Upon seeing this situation, Yuan loudly said, “Not good, this is an ambush! Formations!” Then everyone immediately went into a circle formation. At the same time, Zhao Hai released a large number of Undead as he surveyed the situation around them.

The tree spirits didn’t immediately attack Zhao Hai and the others. Instead, they stopped when they got close. Then a few Sprites walked in between the tree spirits. The leader of the Sprites was someone that Zhao Hai hadn’t seen before. This Sprite looked very young. His eyes were half-open as if he wasn’t interested in the things around him.

Zhao Hai didn’t know what these Sprites were planning to do. Instead of attacking, they paused. Do they want to talk? Was it that if they don’t talk, their mouths will itch?

When the Sprites reached about 100 meters away, the lead Sprite looked at the group. Then his eyes stopped on Zhao Hai as he said, “Zhao Hai, we finally meet.”

Zhao Hai as well as Yuan and the others couldn’t help but stare. They thought that the ambush was for Yuan and the others. Why is the situation not what they expected?

Zhao Hai looked at the Sprite and said, “Who are you? Do we know each other?”

The Sprite chuckled and said, “You do not know me, but I have heard of you. I came here today for you. My name is Murdoch. My friends here in the Six Realms Battlefield have given me face and called me the Golden Sprite!”

Upon hearing the Golden Sprite nickname, Zhao Hai could feel Yuan sucking in cold breath. Zhao Hai looked at Yuan in confusion. Yuan smiled bitterly and said, “Golden Sprite is a formidable Nascent Soul expert of the Sprites. It has been a long time since he made a move. Rumors say that he’s only half-step away from Transcending Tribulation. His life source spirit is a metal spirit. His spirit can be very hard or be soft and can transform into any weapon. It is very powerful. He is said to be invincible under Transcending Tribulation.”

Zhao Hai asked, “Even Cultivators aren’t his opponent?”

Yuan bitterly nodded and said, “Correct. Even Cultivators aren’t his opponents. This is because he went to Yellowsand Planet once and condensed astral qi into his body. This made his attacks very powerful.”

As soon as Zhao Hai heard Yuan say this, his eyes lit up. Then he turned to Murdoch and cupped his fist as he said, “So it turns out to be Elder Golden Sprite. It’s an honor that you came here personally. So why did the elder come here today?”

Murdoch looked at Zhao Hai, then he suddenly laughed as he said, “This old man wanted to see you. I heard that you are a very rare genius of the Machine Field. Originally, this old man didn’t believe the rumors, but now this old man is convinced. Hahaha. You can still keep your calm even after knowing who this old man is. Very good, very good.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Did Senior come for me? If that is the case, then this Zhao Hai will not run. However, how about Senior let the others go?”

Murdoch laughed and said, “Zhao Hai, don’t ruin this old man’s impression of you. You’re a smart kid, so you should know that these people cannot escape today. Moreover, do you think that this old man doesn’t know that you can use space magic? If you want to run, then even this old man will have trouble stopping you. Zhao Hai, you will die today. If you run, then this old man will order the death of everyone from the Machine Field.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “So if I don’t run, Senior wouldn’t kill them? It would be better for me to run and then take revenge later on. Wouldn’t that be better?”

Murdoch smiled and said, “You’re not that kind of person. If you run now and ignore these people, then you are no longer worth this old man’s attention.”

Zhao Hai just smiled and didn’t say anything. Murdoch looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, you’re outstanding, too outstanding that you’re becoming a threat to the Sprites. Therefore, you must die today. This old man even came here today. After all, I can’t help having an excellent young man die in my hands.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh as he said, “Senior, you seem to be very confident that you can hold me back.”

Murdoch smiled faintly. His smile showed his confidence. Then he waved his hand, signalling to the Sprites to return. Then when they returned, stone spirits, earth spirits, wind spirits, and tree spirits began their attack.

Zhao Hai released 20 thousand Undead to combat the approaching spirits. Moreover, the Undead that Zhao Hai released weren’t only Skeletons, he also released Vampires, Lich, and Zombies. When these Undead appeared, Yuan and the others couldn’t help but get startled. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have this many undead. Even Xiong Li and the others were surprised. They didn’t know that Zhao Hai had so many types of Undead.

However, Xiong Li and the others knew that this wasn’t everything that Zhao Hai had. This was because they saw Zhao Hai release more Undead back in the Bug Caves.

The Sprites were similarly startled. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have so many Undead. However, they already prepared for this scenario. A large number of trees and stones were made into spirits by the Sprites.

Both sides were in a stalemate for a while. Meanwhile. Yuan and the others didn’t have a chance to attack. Some people originally wanted to release sword qi to help Zhao Hai. However, they were stopped by Yuan. Yuan knew that Zhao Hai was currently forcing the Sprites to use their life source spirits. And these life source spirits weren’t easy to deal with. It would be very hard for Yuan and the others to join the fight.

Sure enough, when the Sprites saw that their normal spirits weren’t able to threaten Zhao Hai, some of them immediately released their own life source spirits. Then they had these life source spirits join the fight.

With how strong life source spirits were, as soon as they joined the fight, the situation quickly reversed. The Undead released by Zhao Hai began to be pushed back repeatedly. Yuan and the others were now preparing to make a move.

However, Zhao Hai still didn’t take action. This was because the Sprites who released their life source spirits were at Core Formation Strength. Moreover, they only numbered 200. The Sprites had yet to give their best.

Although the Undead were being pushed back, they were still tenaciously holding off the attacks of the Sprites. This caused Murdoch’s expression to turn ugly. They already dispatched so many people and even used 200 life source spirits, yet they were still unable to deal with Zhao Hai. This caused the Sprites to lose face. Murdoch waved his hand causing 300 more life source spirits entering the battle.

This time, Zhao Hai’s side began to crumble. Zhao Hai only released the Undead to temporarily stop the Sprites spirit summons, not life source spirits. Large numbers of Undead began to be eliminated, their soul fires were being put out.

Zhao Hai felt aggrieved by this. He didn’t want to show off a lot of his strength, so he could only release these Undead. But now, these Undead were beginning to die. This caused Zhao Hai to feel distressed.